A Guide to the Cary Reich papers FA1275
Rockefeller Archive Center
Cary Reich papers
1950s-1980s (Bulk 1982)
Rockefeller Archive Center
Reich, Cary
Linden, Patricia
FA1275
13.86 Cubic Feet 10 standard record storage boxes, 10 document boxes containing 565 audio cassettes, and 2 record storage boxes containing special formats.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
This collection primarily contains transcripts, audiotapes, and notes of interviews conducted by author Cary Reich during research for the first volume, and anticipated second volume, of "The Life of Nelson A. Rockefeller." Additionally, it contains partial audiotaped interviews for Reich's New York Times expose "The Creative Mind: The Innovator," which appeared on April 21, 1985, as well as for other financial articles.
In addition, there are audio interviews conducted by Patricia Linden for a "Town and Country" magazine article ("The Rockefellers' Monumental Legacy," September 1982) describing the Rockefeller legacy in New York, as well as for her own unrealized, unauthorized biography of Nelson Rockefeller.
Lastly, the collection has subject files primarily consisting of research materials and news clippings pertaining to a variety of significant events in Nelson Rockfeller's professional life, including but not limited to the 1964 U.S. presidential campaign, the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), his tenure as Governor of New York, and the U.S. vice presidency.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Papers were transferred to RAC in 2012 by the estate of Cary Reich.
Sound recordings
- Interview Transcripts and Subject Files, undated; 1; 12 Cubic Feet
  - Donald Rumsfeld, Interview 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    White House Chief of Staff during President Gerald Ford's administration.
  - Max Abramovitz Interview (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Architect and business partner of Wallace Harrison.
  - Al Abrams Interview (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Worked on Nelson Rockefeller's campaigns for the Republican presidential nomination in 1964 and 1968.
  - Harry Albright Interview (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Deputy Secretary to the Governor; Appointments Officer; New York State Banking Supervisor; Special Counsel to the Vice President; Adirondacks Park Commission
  - Meade Alcorn Interview (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Chair of the Republic National Committee during President Dwight D. Eisenhower's second administration.
  - Robert Alton, Interview 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Nelson Rockefeller met Alton as a classmate at the Lincoln School in New York and later included him in the establishment of the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC).
  - Robert Alton, Interview 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Edward J. Amann Jr., Interview 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Republican member of the New York State Assembly in the 1950s and 1960s.
  - Edward J. Amann Jr., Interview 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - James Andre Interview (Box 1, Folder 10)
    New York State Republican committee chair and then Clinton County Republican chair. He previously was a state trooper and worked security at the State House in Albany.
  - Richard Aurelio Interview (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Journalist; Campaign Manager for New York Mayor John Lindsay in 1969.
  - Doug Barclay Interview (Box 1, Folder 12)
    New York State Senator
  - Peter Berle Interview (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Democratic member of New York State Assembly in 1960s and 1970s.
  - Lee Bolton Interview (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Photographer of art; collaborated with Nelson Rockefeller on art books projects.
  - Joan Braden Interview (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Employee of Rockefeller Family Office in Room 5600; International Basic Economies Corporation; U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; Critical Choices Commission
  - Tom Braden Interview (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Journalist and former CIA employee; husband of Joan Braden.
  - Jack Bronston Interview (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Democratic member of New York State Senate in the 1960s.
  - Richard A. Brown Interview (Box 1, Folder 18)
    New York City Legislative representative in the 1970s.
  - Joseph Bruno Interview (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Gubernatorial campaign aid.
  - Kershaw Burbank Interview (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Campaign aid; Family Office associate.
  - Edward Cain Interview (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Chair of the Genesee County (New York) Republican Committee.
  - Donald Campbell Interview (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Republican member of the New York State Assembly in the 1950s and 1960s. He was also chair of the Montgomery County (New York) Republican Committee.
  - James Cannon Interview (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Gubernatorial and Vice Presidential aide for Congressional matters
  - Joseph Carlino Interview (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Republican Majority Leader of New York State Assembly in the 1950s and Speaker in the 1960s.
  - Gene Case Interview (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Advertising executive who worked on Nelson Rockefeller's third campaign for Governor of New York in 1966.
  - Edward Conway Interview (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Albany County (New York) Republican Chair.
  - Lee Chilcote Interview (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Classmate of Nelson Rockefeller at Darmouth College in the 1920s.
  - Brian Conboy Interview (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Campaign Manager for Charles Goodell, U.S. Senator from New York.
  - Sol Neil Corbin Interview (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Assistant Counsel to the Governor; Counsel to the Governor; Assistant to the Governor in the Attica riot investigation; Special Counsel to the Vice President for the Commission on CIA Activities
  - Edward N. Costikyan Interview (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Chair of New York County Democratic Committee in 1960s; appointed by Nelson Rockefeller to commission that investigated New York City government in 1970s.
  - Jerry Danzig Interview (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Special Assistant to the Governor for Radio and Television
  - Sidney Davidoff Interview (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Administrative Assistant to New York Mayor John V. Lindsay in the 1960s.
  - Dominick DiCarlo Interview (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Republican member of New York State Assembly from the 1960s to the early 1980s. Noteably, DiCarlo was the only Republican in the Assembly to vote against the Rockfeller Drug Laws in the early 1970s.
  - George Dudley, Interview 1, 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Architect; Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs; International Basic Economies Corporation; New York State Office of Regional Development; Pure Water Authority
  - George Dudley, Interview 2 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - George Dudley, Interview 3 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Peter Edelman Interview (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Served on Arthur Goldberg's unsuccessful New York gubernatorial campaign in 1970 as Issues Director.
  - Julius Edelstein Interview (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Served as Executive Assistant to New York Mayor Robet F. Wagner in the 1960s.
  - Meade Esposito Interview (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Served as Brooklyn Democratic Chair.
  - Sam Gould Interview (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Chancellor of the State University of New York (SUNY) system.
  - Hugh and Kay Gregg and Bert Teague Interview (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Hugh Gregg led Nelson Rockefeller's Presidential campaign in New Hampshire in 1964. Teague was a campaign aide in New Hampshire.
  - Robert Grimm and Louis Russo Interview (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Grimm served as Erie County (New York) Republican Chair. Russo was Erie County budget director.
  - Herbert B. Halberg Interview (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Special New York City field coordinator for Governor Rockefeller's 1970 reelection bid. Former Commissioner of Marine and Aviation in Mayor John Lindsay's administration.
  - Raymond Harding Interview (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Bronx County Liberal Party chair; New York State Liberal Party chair.
  - Ellen Harrison Interview (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Ellen Milton Harrison was wife of Wallace K. Harrison, architect and friend of Nelson Rockefeller. She was also the sister of David Milton, husband of Abby (Babs) Rockefeller, who was Nelson Rockefeller's sister.
  - Kitty Carlisle Hart Interview (Box 1, Folder 46)
    She was an actress and special advisor to Governor Nelson Rockefeller on opportunities for women.
  - James Helmuth Interview (Box 1, Folder 47)
    James Helmuth was a campaign aide to Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Ben Hewitt Interview (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Ben Hewitt was the Niagara County (NY) Republican leader.
  - Francis Horn Interview (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Friend of Nelson Rockefeller from their years at Dartmouth College.
  - T. Norman Hurd Interview (Box 2, Folder 50)
    New York State Budget Director; Housing Finance Authority; Advisor to the Governor on Attica Prison riot
  - Hollis Ingraham Interview (Box 2, Folder 51)
    New York State Commissioner of Health
  - John Johnson Interview (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Served on New York State Dormitory Authority during Governor Nelson Rockefeller's administration.
  - John Innes Interview (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Active in New York State Republican Party in the 1960s.
  - Philip Johnson Interview (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Johnson was a noted architect whose association with Nelson Rockefeller began in the early 1930s, when they both served on the Junior Advisory Committee of the Museum of Modern Art, and continued throughout the Governor's lifetime.
  - Betsy Kaplan Interview (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Kaplan was St. Lawrence County (NY) Republican chair in the 1970s.
  - Edward Kimball Interview (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Employee of Venezuela Basic Ecomony Corporation (VBEC), which was founded by Nelson Rockefeller. Specifically, he managed INLACA, which was VBEC's successful milk pasteurization company.
  - Mary Kresky Interview (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Associate of Nelson Rockefeller, worked in his personal office at the Rockefeller Family Office in Manhattan.
  - Alexander Lankler Interview (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Campaign aide for Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Churchill Lathrop Interview (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Professor of art history at Dartmouth College while Nelson Rockefeller was an undergraduate. He went on to collaborate with Nelson and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, co-founder of the Museum of Modern Art, to develop the modern art collection at Dartmouth.
  - Richard Lawrence Interview (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Worked on the Temporary Study Commission on the Future of the Adirondacks and later was appointed by Governor Nelson Rockefeller as the first chair of the Adirondack Park Agency in 1971.
  - Louis Lefkowitz Interview (Box 2, Folder 61)
    New York State Attorney General.
  - Henry Lengyel Interview (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Jefferson County (NY) Republican Chair.
  - Harvey Lipset Interview (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Democratic New York State Assemblyman from 1957 to 1968.
  - John Lindsay Interview (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Mayor of New York during much of Nelson Rockefeller's tenure as Governor of New York. Lindsay was a Republican who switched to the Democratic party while serving as Mayor.
  - John Lockwood, Interview 1 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    Legal counsel to the Rockefeller family
  - John Lockwood, Interview 2 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - John Lockwood, Interview 3 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - John Lockwood, Interview 3 (Box 11, Folder 67a)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted material
  - Bill Lovelock Interview (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Was a detective lieutenant in the New York Police Department and served as a bodyguard for Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Collins Lyden Interview (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Campaign aide to Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Hamilton Fish Interview (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Likely Hamilton Fish IV, a New York Republican who served in the U.S. House of Representatives for 13 terms in the latter half of the 20th century.
  - Harold Fisher Interview (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Served as chair of the Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) during Governor Nelson Rockefeller's tenure.
  - Peter Fishbein Interview (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Served in Nelson Rockfeller's 1968 Presidential campaign; campaign manager for Arthur Goldberg's unsuccessful 1970 New York gubernatorial campaign.
  - Bayard Stuyvesant Forster Interview (Box 2, Folder 73)
    Served as New York State commission of transportation under Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Eleanor Clark French Interview (Box 2, Folder 74)
    Cousin of Mary Clark Rockefeller, wife of John French (NAR's roommate at Dartmouth) and a Democratic activist who was the national president of Americans for Democratic Action.
  - Major Edward Galvin Interview (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Served as a body guard for Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Pat Goldman Interview (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Chair of the Republican Women's Task Force
  - Harmon Goldstone Interview (Box 2, Folder 77)
    An accomplished architect who knew Nelson Rockefeller dating back to their years at the Lincoln School in Manhattan.
  - William Golub Interview (Box 2, Folder 78)
    An attorney who served as Special Assistant to Governor Nelson Rockefeller for rail and commuter problems. He was also special consultant to the Moreland Act Commission to draft legislation that created sweeping changes in New York State's liquor laws.
  - Donna Mitchell Interview (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Was a long-time associate of Nelson Rockefeller, beginning with his service in the Eisenhower administration on the committee to reorganize the federal government (PACGO/SCOGO) and then the newly created Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
  - Richard Wiebe Interview (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Served under Nelson Rockefeller in the New York State Program Office on the program that led to the Pure Waters Act; also on Adirondacks Park Commission.
  - Richard Ottinger Interview (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Democrat who served as U.S. Representative for the 24th and later 25th districts of New York from the 1960s to 1980s.
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 11 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Secretary to the Governor; 1968 Presidential campaign staff; President of Rockefeller Center, Inc.
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 1 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    Married Nelson Rockefeller in 1963.
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 1 (Box 11, Folder 83a)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Laurance Rockefeller Interview (Box 11, Folder 85)
    Nelson Rockefeller's brother.
  - Laurance Rockefeller Interview (Box 11, Folder 85a)
  - Robert MacCrate Interview (Box 2, Folder 86)
    Counsel to the Governor
  - Robert McEwen Interview (Box 2, Folder 87)
    Republican New York state senator, 1954-1964, and a member of the U.S. House of Representatives, 1965-1981.
  - Jean McKee Interview (Box 2, Folder 88)
    Served as an aide to Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Charles McWhorter Interview (Box 2, Folder 89)
    Lawyer and aide to Richard Nixon.
  - Ronald Maiorana Interview, 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 90-91)
    Press secretary for Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Joseph Margiotta Interview (Box 2, Folder 92)
    New York State Assembly member from Uniondale, 1966 to 1976, and Nassau County (NY) Republican chair from 1968 to 1983.
  - John Marchi Interview (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Served as Republican New York state senator from Staten Island.
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 1 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 2 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 3 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 4 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 5 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 6 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - June Martin Interview (Box 3, Folder 100)
    Campaign aide to Governor Nelson Rockefeller
  - Steven Martindale Interview (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Tanya Melich Interview (Box 3, Folder 102)
    Aide to Governor Nelson Rockefeller
  - Donna Mitchell Interview (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - George Mitrovich Interview (Box 3, Folder 104)
    Press secretary for U.S. Senator Charles Goodell, who was apppointed by Governor Nelson Rockefeller to fill the seat after Senator Robert F. Kennedy's assassination in 1968. Interview was conducted by telephone rather than in person.
  - Jonathan Moore Interview (Box 3, Folder 105)
    During the 1968 Republican presidential primaries, Moore was foreign policy advisor to Michigan Governor George Romney and then foreign policy advisor to Governor Nelson Rockefeller after Romney dropped out of the race for the nomination.
  - Edward Morrison Interview (Box 3, Folder 106)
    Leader of the Liberal Party of New York
  - Neal Moylan Interview (Box 3, Folder 107)
    Served as New York Commissioner of Commerce.
  - Milton Musicus Interview (Box 3, Folder 108)
    Served Governor Nelson Rockefeller as Assistant Secretary for Administration.
  - Roy Neuberger Interview (Box 3, Folder 109)
    Financier, philanthropist, and art collector who knew Governor Nelson Rockefeller throught their mutual love of modern art.
  - Bernard Newman Interview (Box 3, Folder 110)
    Counsel to the New York State Republican Party and then appointed to the New York State Supreme Court by Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Frank O'Connor Interview (Box 3, Folder 111)
    District attorney of Queens County, New York, and Democratic nominee for governor in 1966. Interview included his aid Jim O'Donnell.
  - Gen. Theodore Parker Interview (Box 3, Folder 112)
    General Parker (U.S. Army) first served on the staff of Nelson Rockfeller during his tenure in the Eisenhower Administation as Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs. Parker later served as New York State Commissioner of Transporation.
  - Roswell B. Perkins, Interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    Staff of Nelson Rockefeller while he was Eisenhower's Assistant Secretary for U.S. Health, Education, and Welfare Department; First Counsel to the Governor for Nelson Rockefeller; Platform planning for 1960 and 1964 Presidential Campaigns.
  - Roswell B. Perkins, Interview 3 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Fiorvante (Fred) Perotta Interview (Box 3, Folder 115)
    Assistant counsel to the Governor for Nelson Rockefeller; then New York City coordinator of Rockefeller's 1970 gubernatorial campaign.
  - Haywood Plumadore Interview (Box 3, Folder 116)
    New York Republican who served as Harrietstown Town Attorney and Supervisor; later was in the State Assembly representing Franklin County and as county chair for the Republican party.
  - John Price Interview (Box 3, Folder 117)
    Campaign aide for Governor Nelson Rockefeller's 1968 presidential campaign.
  - Robert Price, Interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    Managed Nelson Rockefeller's 1964 Republican presidential primary campaign for Oregon.
  - Robert Price, Interview 2 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Thomas Prideaux Interview (Box 3, Folder 120)
    Classmate of Nelson Rockefeller from the Lincoln School in Manhattan.
  - Robert Purcell Interview (Box 3, Folder 121)
    Served as president of the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC).
  - Lee Robb Interview (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - David Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    Restricted material. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted.
    Youngest brother of Nelson Rockefeller
  - David Rockefeller, Interview 1 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Nelson Rockefeller, Jr. Interview (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Margaret Woodell Interview (Box 3, Folder 126)
    Interview was conducted by phone rather than in person.
  - William Sharkey, Interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - William Sharkey Interview, Interview 2 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Oscar Ruebhausen, Interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Oscar Ruebhausen, Interview 2 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Bernard Ruggieri Interview (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Ryan Interview (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - St. Thomas Interview (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Walther Moreira Salles Interview, 1989; 42 pages (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Fred Scribner Interview (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - George Shapiro Interview (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Leslie Slote Interview (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Robert Stafford Interview (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Stanley Steingut Interview (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Linda Jamieson Storrow, Interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    Worked in Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs; spouse of Public Relations Director (Frank Jamieson) for Nelson Rockefeller's first campaign for the U.S. presidency in 1960.
  - Linda Jamieson Storrow, Interview 2 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Jack Terry Interview (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Jack Terry Interview - II (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Marley Thaler Interview (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Craig Thorne Interview (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Trubin Interview (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Jacob Underhill Interview (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Jack Vandervort Interview (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Edward Van Ness Interview (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Andrew Von Hirsh Interview (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Robert Wagner Interview (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - John Walsh Interview (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Edward Warburg Interview (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - F. Clifton White Interview (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Charles Widmayer Interview (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - J. Walker Wiggin Interview (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Nadia Williams Interview, 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 157-158)
  - Malcolm Wilson Interview (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Malcolm Wilson Interview - II (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Malcolm Wilson Interview - III (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Wolfgang Interview (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Albert and Virginia Callan Interview (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Alexander (Sam) Aldrich Interview (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Edward Koch Interview (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Lloyd Free Interview (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 9 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Richard Rosenbaum Interview (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Henry Diamond Interview (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Margot Lindsay Interview (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Franklin Lindsay Interview (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Paul Curran Interview (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Bill Watts Interview (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Milton Gwirtzmann Interview (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Joseph Canzeri Interview (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Richard Nathan Interview (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - David Goldberg Interview (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 7 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Harold Stassen Interview (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - George Romney Interview (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Bruce Gyory Interview (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Gillies Interview (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Robert Bennett Interview (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Susan Herter Interview (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Edward Kresky Interview - I & II (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Ted Van Dyk Interview (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Lerner & Kunzman Interview (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Warren Anderson Interview (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - John Burns Interview (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Clinton Dominick Interview (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Kuhnen Interview (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Carl Spad Interview (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Malcolm Wilson Interview - IV (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - F. Clifton White Interview - II (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Thomas Mackell Interview (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Joseph Boyd Interview - II (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Jack Bigel Interview (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Stephan Duggan Interview (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Murray Gart Interview (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Jack McEnany Interview (Box 5, Folder 200)